SAME DAY SHIPPING MADE IN THE USA FREE US SHIPPING $79+

Search

[

](https://hugeminis.com/)

Search

Menu

[Home](https://hugeminis.com/) / Privacy Policy

Privacy Policy
==============

Privacy Policy
==============

### TL;DR

We respect your privacy and do our utmost to make sure that your personal information remains private. We have never, and will never sell or intentionally make public, any personal information gathered on this site.

### Policy Overview

This Policy describes the information we collect and use when you visit or make a purchase from our site. It also covers how that information is used, and your options regarding what happens with the information that you provide us.

### Personal Information

If you make a transaction on our site, there’s some personal information that’s required to fulfill your order. This includes your name, email, phone number, billing/shipping address, and payment information. We use this order information to process your payment, arrange for shipping, and provide you with confirmation and shipping details. We use Stripe and PayPal for payment processing, who may alternatively collect and store payment transaction data on their own servers.

### Cookies

We use cookies (a small piece of data transferred to your device) to remember information such as items added to the shopping cart. They are also used for record keeping. You may deactivate or restrict the sending of cookies in your web browser settings. Cookies that are already stored may be deleted at any time.

### Tracking

We use anonymized data to improve our site. We will store the page from which you visited us from, the parts of our site you visit, the date and duration of your visit, and information about the device that was used during your visit. We do not allow third party tracker networks to record your activity on this site.

### Opt-out of website tracking

### Email

If you subscribe to our email list using a newsletter form, or opt-in during the checkout step, you can expect to receive news or promotional email communications. If you no longer wish to be included, you can click the unsubscribe link in any of the email messages, or contact us [here](https://hugeminis.com/contact-us/).

### Retention of data

The information covered here is retained on a secure server for use by us as reference. None of the personal information obtained by us will ever be sold, intentionally made public, or used in any way other than what’s listed. You can contact us in regards to the personal information we may hold about you and to ask that your personal information be corrected, updated, or deleted. If you wish to do this, please contact us [here](https://hugeminis.com/contact-us/).

_**Last updated:** November 20, 2020_

**Same Day Shipping**  
Orders placed before 12PM  
EST are shipped same day.

**Money Back Guarantee**  
Did your plans change?  
Return for a full refund.

**Hand Made in the USA**  
We’re proud to make all our  
products in house by hand.

**Free Shipping**  
Spend $79+ for  
free US shipping.

**Same Day Shipping**Orders placed before 12PM EST ship same day.

**Money Back Guarantee**Did your plans change? Return for a full refund.

**Hand Made in the USA**All of our products are made in house by hand.

**Free Shipping**Orders over $79 qualify for free US shipping.

EST. 2017 

NEWS Stay informed about promotions and new product releases for tabletop gaming.

Made in USA Our art and scale modeling products are made by hand in the USA. 

Programs

Social

Links

© Huge Miniatures
